Inventory of the Frank and Doris Hursely papers, 1942-1969
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Frank and Doris Hursley Papers
1942-1969
Hursley, Frank
64.00 cubic ft.
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
02937
Papers for these radio and television writers.
Biography
Frank and Doris Hursley wrote drama and comedy programs for radio and serial dramas for both radio and television.
Scope and Content Note
Collection includes mainly scripts for radio programs (1943-1954) written by the Hursleys along with correspondence and other related materials. There are also scripts for two television soap operas, "Search for Tomorrow" (1957-1964) and "The Guiding Light" (1963-1969). One of the radio programs, "Service to the Front" dramatized World War II incidents and experiences of soldiers which were furnished by the U.S. War Department. One episode dramatized the dropping of the first atomic bomb and was broadcast the day following the bombing. There are also letters from servicemen commenting on the show. The radio program "American Women" dramatized homefront activities of women during World War II.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the repository's online public access catalog.
Hursley, Doris; Television authorship.; Soap operas -- United States.; Radio plays -- United States.; Radio serials.; Television plays -- United States.; Television serials -- United States.; Radio comedies -- United States.; Radio authorship.; World War, 1939-1945 -- Drama -- United States.; World War, 1939-1945 -- War work -- United States.; World War, 1939-1945 -- United States.; Scripts; Radio writers; Search for tomorrow (Television program); General hospital (Television program); Websters (Radio program); Truitts (Radio program); That's rich (Radio program); American women (Radio program); Cousin Willie (Radio program); Life is what you make it (Radio program); Light of the world (Radio program); Service to the front (Radio program)
Arts, Humanities, and Social Sciences; Performing Arts; Social Life and Customs; People, Ethnicity, and Culture
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions on the materials for research purposes, and the collection is open to the public.
Related Materials
There are no known other archival collections created by Frank and Doris Hursley at the date of processing.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Frank and Doris Hursley in 1968.
Container List
- General Hospital
  - Script Number 1-5, April 1-5, 1963 (Box 1)
    Week #1
  - Script Number 6-10, April 8-12, 1963 (Box 1)
    Week #2
  - Script Number 11-15, April 15-19, 1963 (Box 1)
    Week #3
  - Script Number 16-20, April 22-26, 1963 (Box 1)
    Week #4
  - Script Number 21-25, April 29-May 3, 1963 (Box 1)
    Week #5
  - Script Number 26-30, May 6-10, 1963 (Box 2)
    Week #6
  - Script Number 31-35, May 13-17, 1963 (Box 2)
    Week #7
  - Script Number 36-40, May 20-24, 1963 (Box 2)
    Week #8
  - Script Number 41-45, May 27-31, 1963 (Box 2)
    Week #9
  - Script Number 46-50, June 3-7, 1963 (Box 2)
    Week #10
  - Script Number 51-55, June 10-14, 1963 (Box 3)
    Week #11
  - Script Number 56-60, June 17-21, 1963 (Box 3)
    Week #12
  - Script Number 61-65, June 24-28, 1963 (Box 3)
    Week #13
  - Script Number 66-70, July 1-5, 1963 (Box 3)
    Week #14
  - Script Number 71-75, July 8-12, 1963 (Box 3)
    Week #15
  - Script Number 76-80, July 15-19, 1963 (Box 4)
    Week #16
  - Script Number 81-85, July 22-26, 1963 (Box 4)
    Week #17
  - Script Number 86-90, July 29-August 2, 1963 (Box 4)
    Week #18
  - Script Number #91-#95, August 5-9, 1963 (Box 4)
    Week #19
  - Script Number 96-100, August 12-16, 1963 (Box 4)
    Week #20
  - Script Number 101-105, August 19-23, 1963 (Box 4)
    Week #21
  - Script Number 106-110, August 26-30, 1963 (Box 5)
    Week #22
  - Script Number 111-115, September 2-6, 1963 (Box 5)
    Week #23
  - Script Number 116-120, September 9-13, 1963 (Box 5)
    Week #24
  - Script Number 121-125, September 16-20, 1963 (Box 5)
    Week #25
  - Script Number 126-130, September 23-27, 1963 (Box 5)
    Week #26
  - Script Number 131-135, September 30-October 4, 1963 (Box 6)
    Week #27
  - Script Number 136-140, October 7-11, 1963 (Box 6)
    Week #28
  - Script Number 141-145, October 14-19, 1963 (Box 6)
    Week #29
  - Script Number 146-150, October 21-25, 1963 (Box 6)
    Week #30
  - Script Number 151-155, October 28-November 1, 1963 (Box 6)
    Week #31
  - Script Number 156-160, November 4-8, 1963 (Box 7)
    Week #32
  - Script Number 161-165, November 11-15, 1963 (Box 7)
    Week #33
  - Script Number 168-170, November 18-22, 1963 (Box 7)
    Week #34
  - Script Number 171-175, November 25-29, 1963 (Box 7)
    Week #35
  - Script Number 176-180, December 2-6, 1963 (Box 7)
    Week #36
  - Script Number 181-184 (no 185), December 9-13, 1963 (Box 8)
    Week #37
  - Script Number 186-190, December 16-28, 1963 (Box 8)
    Week #3 8
  - Script Number 191-195, December 23-27, 1963 (Box 8)
    Week #39
  - Script Number 1-5 (no 3), December 30-January3, 1964 (Box 8)
    Week #40
  - Script Number 6-10, January 6-10, 1964 (Box 8)
    Week #41
  - Script Number 11-15, January 13-17, 1964 (Box 9)
    Week #42
  - Script Number 16-20, January 20-26, 1964 (Box 9)
    Week #43
  - Script Number 21-25, January 27-31, 1964 (Box 9)
    Week #44
  - Script Number 26-30, February 3-7, 1964 (Box 9)
    Week #45
  - Script Number 31-35, February 10-14, 1964 (Box 9)
    Week #46
  - Script Number 36-40, February 17-21, 1964 (Box 10)
    Week #47
  - Script Number 41-45, February 24-28, 1964 (Box 10)
    Week #48
  - Script Number 46-50, March 2-6, 1964 (Box 10)
    Week #49
  - Script Number 51-55, March 9-13, 1964 (Box 10)
    Week #50
  - Script Number 56-60, March 16-20, 1964 (Box 11)
    Week #51
  - Script Number 61-65, March 23-27, 1964 (Box 11)
    Week #52
  - Script Number 66-70, March 30-April 3, 1964 (Box 11)
    Week #53
  - Script Number 71-75, April 6-10, 1964 (Box 11)
    Week #54
  - Script Number 76-80, April 13-17, 1964 (Box 11)
    Week #55
  - Script Number 81-85, April 20-24, 1964 (Box 11)
    Week #56
  - Script Number 86-90, April 27-May 1, 1964 (Box 11)
    Week #57
  - Script Number 91-95, May 4-8, 1964 (Box 12)
    Week #58
  - Script Number 96-100, May 11-15, 1964 (Box 12)
    Week #59
  - Script Number 101-105, May 18-22, 1964 (Box 12)
    Week #60
  - Script Number 106-110, May 25-29, 1964 (Box 12)
    Week #61
  - Script Number 111-116, June 1-5, 1964 (Box 12)
    Week #62
  - Script Number 116-120, June 8-12, 1964 (Box 12)
    Week #63
  - Script Number 121-125, June 15-19, 1964 (Box 13)
    Week #64
  - Script Number 126-130, June 22-26, 1964 (Box 13)
    Week #65
  - Script Number 131-135, June 29-July 3, 1964 (Box 13)
    Week #66
  - Script Number 136-140, July 6-10, 1964 (Box 13)
    Week #67
  - Script Number 141-155, July 13-17, 1964 (Box 13)
    Week #68
  - Script Number 146-150, July 20-24, 1964 (Box 14)
    Week #69
  - Script Number 151-155, July 27-31, 1964 (Box 14)
    Week #70
  - Script Number 156-160, August 3-7, 1964 (Box 14)
    Week #71
  - Script Number 161-165, August 10-14, 1964 (Box 14)
    Week #72
  - Script Number 166-170, August 17-21, 1964 (Box 14)
    Week #73
  - Script Number 171-175, August 24-28, 1964 (Box 15)
    Week #74
  - Script Number 176-180, August 31-September 4, 1964 (Box 15)
    Week #75
  - Script Number 181-185, September7-11, 1964 (Box 15)
    Week #76
  - Script Number 186-190, September 14-18, 1964 (Box 15)
    Week #77
  - Script Number 191-195, September 21-25, 1964 (Box 16)
    Week #78
  - Script Number 196-200, September 28- October 2, 1964 (Box 16)
    Week #79
  - Script Number 201-205, October 5-9, 1964 (Box 16)
    Week #80
  - Script Number 206-210, October 12-16, 1964 (Box 16)
    Week #81
  - Script Number 211-215, October 19-23, 1964 (Box 17)
    Week #82
  - Script Number 216-220, October 26-30, 1964 (Box 17)
    Week #83
  - Script Number 221-225, November 2-6, 1964 (Box 17)
    Week #84
  - Script Number 226-230, November 9-13, 1964 (Box 17)
    Week #85
  - Script Number 231-235, November 16-20, 1964 (Box 18)
    Week #86
  - Script Number 236-240, November 23-27, 1964 (Box 18)
    Week #87
  - Script Number 241-245, November 30-December 4, 1964 (Box 18)
    Week #88
  - Script Number 246-250, December 7-11, 1964 (Box 18)
    Week #89
  - Script Number 251-255, December 14-18, 1964 (Box 18)
    Week #90
  - Script Number 256-260, December 21-24, 1964 (Box 19)
    Week #91
  - Script Number 261-265, December 28-31, 1964 (Box 19)
    Week #92
  - Script Number 1-5, January 4-8, 1965 (Box 19)
    Week #93
  - Script Number 6-10, January 11-15, 1965 (Box 19)
    Week #94
  - Script Number 11-15, January 18-22, 1965 (Box 19)
    Week #95
  - Script Number 16-20, January 25-29, 1965 (Box 20)
    Week #96
  - Script Number 21-25, February 1-5, 1965 (Box 20)
    Week #97
  - Script Number 26-30, February 8-12, 1965 (Box 20)
    Week #98
  - Script Number 31-35, February 15-19, 1965 (Box 20)
    Week #99
  - Script Number 36-40, February 22-26, 1965 (Box 20)
    Week #100
  - Script Number 41-45, March 1-5, 1965 (Box 21)
    Week #101
  - Script Number 46-50, March 8-12, 1965 (Box 21)
    Week #102
  - Script Number 51-55, March 15-19, 1965 (Box 21)
    Week #103
  - Script Number 56-60, March 22-26, 1965 (Box 21)
    Week #104
  - Audition Materials for Actors (Box 21)
  - Critical Comments from New York Office of American Broad-Casting Company on First Scripts and Characters and Story Projection (Box 21)
  - Night Time Version Proposal for "General Hospital." (Box 21)
  - Original Proposal for Medical Daytime Serial "Pulse of Life," Including Possible Characters (Box 21)
  - Pilot script for "General Hospital." (Box 21)
  - Potential Pilots(2) for a Medical Series called "Emergency" Hospital." (Box 21)
  - List of Sets Useddin "General Hospital" and the Final, Approved, Scale Drawing of the Sets on Stages (Box 21)
  - First Six Months Story Projection (Box 21)
  - Story Summary After First Six Months of Broadcast (Box 21)
- Correspondence
  - American Women
    - 1942 (Box 22)
    - 1943 (Box 22)
    - 1944 (Box 22)
    - 1945 (Box 22)
  - Service to the Front
    - 1944 (Box 22)
    - 1945 (Box 22)
    - 1946 (Box 22)
- Miscellaneous
  One folder containing a copy of the University of Syracuse Press "Atomic Bombs" and a review of this show from the chicago Tribune
- Radio Scripts
  - American Women
    - July 1, 1943 (Box 22)
    - July 7, 1943 (Box 22)
    - July 8, 1943 (Box 22)
    - July 15, 1943 (Box 22)
    - July 16, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 9, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 10, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 11, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 13, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 16,1943 (Box 22)
    - August17,1943 (Box 22)
    - August 18, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 19, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 20, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 23, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 24, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 25, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 26, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 27, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 30, 1943 (Box 22)
    - August 31, 1943 (Box 22)
    - September 1, 1943 (Box 22)
    - September 2, 1943 (Box 22)
    - September 3, 1943 (Box 22)
    - September 6, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 7, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 8, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 9, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 10, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 13, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 14, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 15, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 16, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 17, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 20, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 21, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 22, 1943 (Box 23)
      Week #38
    - September 23, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 24, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 27, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 28, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 29, 1943 (Box 23)
    - September 30, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 1, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 4, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 5, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 6, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 7, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 8, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 11, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 12, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 13, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 14, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 15, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 18, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 19, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 20, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 21, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 22, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 25, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 26, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 27, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 28, 1943 (Box 23)
    - October 29, 1943 (Box 23)
    - November 1, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 2, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 3, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 4, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 5, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 8, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 9, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 10, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 11, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 12, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 15, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 16, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 17, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 18, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 19, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 22, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 23, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 24, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 25, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 26, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 29, 1943 (Box 24)
    - November 30, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 1, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 2, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 3, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 6, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 7, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 8, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 9, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 10, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 13, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 14, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 15, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 16, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 17, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 20, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 21, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 22, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 23, 1943 (Box 24)
    - December 24, 1943 (Box 24)
      Week #105
    - December 27, 1943 (Box 24)
      Week #106
    - December 28, 1943 (Box 24)
      Week #107
    - December 29, 1943 (Box 24)
      Week #108
    - December 30, 1943 (Box 24)
      Week #109
    - December 31, 1943 (Box 24)
      Week #110
    - January 3, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #111
    - January 4, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #112
    - January 5, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #113
    - January 6, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #114
    - January 7, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #115
    - January 10, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #116
    - January 11, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #117
    - January 12, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #118
    - January 13, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #119
    - January 14, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #120
    - January 17, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #121
    - January 18, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #122
    - January 19, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #123
    - January 20, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #124
    - January 21, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #125
    - January 24, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #126
    - January 25, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #127
    - January 26, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #128
    - January 27, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #129
    - January 28, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #130
    - January 31, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #131
    - February 1, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #132
    - February 2, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #133
    - February 3, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #134
    - February 4, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #135
    - February 7, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #136
    - February 8, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #137
    - February 9, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #138
    - February 10, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #139
    - February 11, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #140
    - February 14, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #141
    - February 15, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #142
    - February 16, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #143
    - February 17, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #144
    - February 18, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #145
    - February 21, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #146
    - February 22, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #147
    - February 23, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #148
    - February 24, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #149
    - February 25, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #150
    - February 28, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #151
    - February 29, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #152
    - March 1, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #153
    - March 2, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #154
    - March 3, 1944 (Box 25)
      Week #155
    - March 6, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #156
    - March 7, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #157
    - March 8, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #158
    - March 9, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #159
    - March 10, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #160
    - March 13, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #161
    - March 14, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #162
    - March 15, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #163
    - March 16, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #164
    - March 17, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #165
    - March 20, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #166
    - March 21, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #167
    - March 22, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #168
    - March 23, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #169
    - March 24, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #170
    - March 27, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #171
    - March 28, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #172
    - March 29, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #173
    - March 30, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #174
    - March 31, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #175
    - April 3, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #176
    - April 4, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #177
    - April 5, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #178
    - April 6, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #179
    - April 7, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #180
    - April 10, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #181
    - April 11, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #182
    - April 12, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #183
    - April 13, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #184
    - April 14, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #185
    - April 17, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #186
    - April 18, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #187
    - April 19, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #188
    - April 20, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #189
    - April 21, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #190
    - April 24, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #191
    - April 25, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #192
    - April 26, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #193
    - April 27, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #194
    - April 28, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #195
    - May 1, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #196
    - May 2, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #197
    - May 3, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #198
    - May 4, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #199
    - May 5, 1944 (Box 26)
      Week #200
    - May 8, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #201
    - May 9, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #202
    - May 10, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #203
    - May 11, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #204
    - May 12, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #205
    - May 15, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #206
    - May 16, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #207
    - May 17, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #208
    - May 18, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #209
    - May 19, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #210
    - May 22, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #211
    - May 23, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #212
    - May 24, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #213
    - May 25, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #214
    - May 26, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #215
    - May 29, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #216
    - May 30, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #217
    - May 31, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #218
    - June 1, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #219
    - June 2, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #220
    - June 5, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #221
    - June 6, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #222
    - June 7, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #223
    - June 8, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #224
    - June 9, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #225
    - June 12, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #226
    - June 13, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #227
    - June 14, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #228
    - June 15, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #229
    - June 16, 1944 (Box 27)
      Week #230
  - Cousin Willye
    - July 6,1953 (Box 27)
    - July 13,1953 (Box 27)
    - July 20,1953 (Box 27)
    - July 27,1953 (Box 27)
    - August 4,1953 (Box 28)
    - August 4, 1953 (Box 28)
    - August 11, 1953 (Box 28)
    - August 24, 1953 (Box 28)
    - September 8, 1953 (Box 28)
    - September 15, 1953 (Box 28)
    - September 22, 1953 (Box 28)
    - September 29, 1953 (Box 28)
    - Audition Scripts (Box 28)
    - Laughs (Box 29)
    - Original Willie (Box 29)
    - Show Records (Box 29)
  - Esther
    Included are two copies of the screenplay and two copies of the screenplay treatment, showing the steps by which the scripts for a radio daytime serial became a viable screenplay.
  - Life Is What You Make It
    - 1-55, (No dates on any of these scripts, but they were used around 1941.) (Box 30)
    - Story Lines (Box 31)
  - The Light of The World
    - June 3, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1621
    - June 4, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1622
    - June 5, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1623
    - June 6, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1624
    - June 7, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1625
    - June 10, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1626
    - June 11, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1627
    - June 12, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1628
    - June 13, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1629
    - June 14, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1630
    - June 17, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1631
    - June 18, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1632
    - June 19, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1633
    - June 20, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1634
    - June 21, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1635
    - June 24, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1636
    - June 25, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1637
    - June 26, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1638
    - June 27, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1639
    - June 28, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1640
    - July 1, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1641
    - July 2, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1642
    - July 3, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1643
    - July 4, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1644
    - July 5, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1645
    - July 8, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1646
    - July 9, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1647
    - July 10, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1648
    - July 11, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1649
    - July 12, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1650
    - July 15, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1651
    - July 16, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1652
    - July 17, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1653
    - July 18, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1654
    - July 19, 1946 (Box 32)
      Week #1655
    - July 22, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1656
    - July 23, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1657
    - July 24, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1658
    - July 25, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1659
    - July 25, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1660
    - July 29, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1661
    - July 30, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1662
    - July 31, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1663
    - August 1, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1664
    - August 2, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1665
    - August 5, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1666
    - August 6, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1667
    - August 7, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1668
    - August 8, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1669
    - August 9, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1670
    - August 12, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1671
    - August 13, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1672
    - August 14, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1673
    - August 15, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1674
    - August 16, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1675
    - August 19, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1676
    - August 20, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1677
    - August 21, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1678
    - August 22, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1679
    - August 23, 1946 (Box 33)
      Week #1680
  - Service to the Front
    - June 23, 1944 (Box 33)
    - June 30, 1944 (Box 33)
    - July 7, 1944 (Box 33)
    - July 14, 1944 (Box 33)
    - July 28, 1944 (Box 33)
    - August 4, 1944 (Box 34)
    - August 11, 1944 (Box 34)
    - August 18, 1944 (Box 34)
    - August 25, 1944 (Box 34)
    - September 1, 1944 (Box 34)
    - September 8, 1944 (Box 34)
    - September 12, 1944 (Box 34)
    - September 19, 1944 (Box 34)
    - September 26, 1944 (Box 34)
    - October 3, 1944 (Box 34)
    - October 10, 1944 (Box 34)
    - October 17, 1944 (Box 34)
    - October 24, 1944 (Box 34)
    - November 14, 1944 (Box 34)